Walter B. Wriston Papers MS134
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Books, 1982 -- 2007; 1982 -- 2006; MS134.002; 7.7 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material, 1999; MS134.002.023.00005 (Box 23)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material, 1990 -- 1998; MS134.002.023.00006 (Box 23)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Early Draft, 2000; MS134.002.023.00007 (Box 23)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Draft, 2000; MS134.002.023.00008 (Box 23)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Draft, 2000; MS134.002.024.00001 (Box 24)
    Walter Wriston stopped working on the book in 2000 and this was the latest version he was editing.
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Draft, 2000; MS134.002.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Photocopy of Draft, 2000; MS134.002.024.00003 (Box 24)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Photocopy of Draft, 2000; MS134.002.024.00004 (Box 24)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Photocopy of Draft, 2000; MS134.002.024.00005 (Box 24)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Draft, 2006; MS134.002.024.00006 (Box 24)
  - Bits, Bytes and Balance Sheets: The New Economic Rules of Engagement in a Wireless World by Walter B. Wriston, 2007; MS134.002.024.00007; Wriston, Walter B. (Box Volume 24)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Untitled Chapter [1 of 2], 1991; MS134.002.038.00063 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Untitled Chapter [2 of 2], 1991; MS134.002.038.00064 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book [1 of 4], 1991; MS134.002.038.00065 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book [2 of 4], 1991; MS134.002.038.00066 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book [3 of 4], 1991; MS134.002.038.00067 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book [4 of 4], 1991; MS134.002.038.00068 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book as of [1 of 2], 1990; MS134.002.038.00069 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book as of [2 of 2], 1990; MS134.002.038.00070 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book on [1 of 4], 1991; MS134.002.038.00071 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book on [2 of 4], 1991; MS134.002.038.00072 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book on [3 of 4], 1991; MS134.002.039.00001 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book on [4 of 4], 1991; MS134.002.039.00002 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book3Aug91 [1 of 4], 1991; MS134.002.039.00003 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book3Aug91 [2 of 4], 1991; MS134.002.039.00004 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book3Aug91 [3 of 4], 1991; MS134.002.039.00005 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book3Aug91 [4 of 4], 1991; MS134.002.039.00006 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book as of [1 of 2], 1991; MS134.002.039.00007 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Book as of [2 of 2], 1991; MS134.002.039.00008 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Foreward, MS134.002.039.00009 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Chapter 1 (Orig, MS134.002.039.00010 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Latest Chapter 2, MS134.002.039.00011 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Latest Chapter 2 April, MS134.002.039.00012 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Latest Chapter 2, 1991; MS134.002.039.00013 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Revised Chapter 3, MS134.002.039.00014 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Backup of Backup of Rewrite Ch [Chapter 3], MS134.002.039.00015 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Rewrite Chapter 3 May 25, MS134.002.039.00016 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Backup of Rewrite Chapter 3 May, MS134.002.039.00017 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Latest Chapter 4, MS134.002.039.00018 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Revised Chapter 6 April, MS134.002.039.00019 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Revised Chapters 5-10, MS134.002.039.00020 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Chapter 12, MS134.002.039.00021 (Box 39)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] Footnotes, MS134.002.039.00022 (Box 39)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets Typescript [Binder] 1 of 2, 2006; MS134.002.039.00023 (Box 39)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets Typescript [Binder] 2 of 2, 2006; MS134.002.039.00024 (Box 39)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets Typescript [Binder] 1 of 2, 2006; MS134.002.039.00025 (Box 39)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets Typescript [Binder] 2 of 2, 2006; MS134.002.039.00026 (Box 39)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets] Manuscript for The Quick and the Dead, 2006; MS134.002.039.00027 (Box 39)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets] Manuscript for The Quick and the Dead, 2006; MS134.002.039.00028 (Box 39)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets] manuscript for the Quick and the Dead, 2006; MS134.002.039.00029 (Box 39)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets 7-10-06 Manuscript Master for duplication, 2006 -- 2007; MS134.002.039.00030 (Box 39)
    This file contains a CD-R titled 'Kathy Wriston'. The CD is an Imation and contains one Microsoft Word document titled, 'WristonBookasof7-10-06'.
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets] Book, MS134.002.040.00001 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets draft] Preface, MS134.002.040.00002 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets] Bytes [Chapter 3 draft], MS134.002.040.00003 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets] Additional material identified for possible inclusion in The Quick and the Dead [Binder] [1 of 2], 2006; MS134.002.040.00004 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets] Additional material identified for possible inclusion in The Quick and the Dead [Binder] [2 of 2], 2006; MS134.002.040.00005 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets] Source material for the Quick and the Dead [Binder] [1 of 4], 2006; MS134.002.040.00006 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets] Source material for the Quick and the Dead [Binder] [2 of 4], 2006; MS134.002.040.00007 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets] Source material for the Quick and the Dead [Binder] [3 of 4], 2006; MS134.002.040.00008 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets] Source material for the Quick and the Dead [Binder] [4 of 4], 2006; MS134.002.040.00009 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets Source Materials Articles and Speeches sent to John McCarty for consideration and review and included in the final manuscript [Binder] 1 of 2, 2006; MS134.002.040.00010 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets Source Materials Articles and Speeches sent to John McCarty for consideration and review and included in the final manuscript [Binder] 2 of 2, 2006; MS134.002.040.00011 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets Source Materials Articles and Speeches sent to John McCarty for consideration and review but not used in the Final Manuscript [Binder] 1 of 4, 2006; MS134.002.040.00012 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets Source Materials Articles and Speeches sent to John McCarty for consideration and review but not used in the Final Manuscript [Binder] 2 of 4, 2006; MS134.002.040.00013 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets Source Materials Articles and Speeches sent to John McCarty for consideration and review but not used in the Final Manuscript [Binder] 3 of 4, 2006; MS134.002.040.00014 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets Source Materials Articles and Speeches sent to John McCarty for consideration and review but not used in the Final Manuscript [Binder] 4 of 4, 2006; MS134.002.040.00015 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets- correspondence and publishing material], MS134.002.040.00016 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Review in Foreign Affairs], MS134.002.040.00017 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets- correspondence and publishing material], MS134.002.040.00018 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
    This file also contains a CD-R titled 'Bits, Bytes, Balance Sheets 2nd Revised Pageproofs - PDF 9/4/07'. The CD-R is a Maxwell and contains one PDF file of 'Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets' by Walter B. Wriston.
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets- correspondence and publishing material], MS134.002.040.00019 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
    This file also contains two CD-Rs, both titled 'Books, Bytes, Balance Sheets By Walter B. Wriston'. The CD-Rs are exactly the same and were created by Shearman and Sterling. Each contains one PDF file of 'Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets' by Walter B. Wriston.
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets] Correspondence, including Henry A. Kissenger, MS134.002.040.00020 (Box MS134 Shared 2)
  - [Walter - files from his office mostly Risk, Elsevier, Twilight, Replica Books] [Envelope], 2005 -- 2007; MS134.002.042.00001 (Box 42)
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - Replica Books/ Baker and Taylor [Walter - files from his office mostly Risk, Elsevier, Twilight, Replica Books] [Envelope], 1991 -- 2002; MS134.002.042.00002 (Box 42)
  - Twilight of Sovereignty [Walter - files from his office mostly Risk, Elsevier, Twilight, Replica Books] [Envelope], 1989 -- 2007; MS134.002.042.00003 (Box 42)
  - Walter B. Wriston [Walter - files from his office mostly Risk, Elsevier, Twilight, Replica Books] [Envelope], 1990; MS134.002.042.00004 (Box 42)
  - Copyright agreement (1/5/04) (J. Beskeen / Elsevier Ltd.) [Walter - files from his office mostly Risk, Elsevier, Twilight, Replica Books] [Envelope], 1985 -- 2004; MS134.002.042.00005 (Box 42)
  - Risk & Other Four Letter Words [Walter - files from his office mostly Risk, Elsevier, Twilight, Replica Books] [Envelope], 2007; MS134.002.042.00006 (Box 42)
  - Risk and Other Four Letter Words by Walter B. Wriston, 1986; MS134.002.046.00001 (Box 46)
  - Risk and Other Four Letter Words, Book Reviews, 1986; MS134.002.046.00002 (Box 46)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Book Proposal, 1987; MS134.002.046.00003 (Box 46)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Source Material for the Introduction, 1984 -- 1987; MS134.002.046.00004 (Box 46)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Source Material for the Introduction, 1986 -- 1987; MS134.002.046.00005 (Box 46)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Source Material for Chapter Two, MS134.002.046.00006 (Box 46)
- Articles and Interviews, 1955 -- 2005; 1984 -- 1999; MS134.003; 3.25 Linear Feet; 36 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains interviews and articles written by, about, or mentioning Walter B. Wriston from 1955-2004. Material in the collection includes original published articles, as well as photocopies and drafts by Wriston. Also included is Wriston's correspondence with editors and/or producers, discussing the particulars of an article or interview. There are also drafts of articles by Wriston which were submitted for publication but were not published. Wriston was interviewed for various programs, including Face the Nation, Meet the Press, Lou Dobbs Moneyline, Lou Dobbs Tonight, Bloomberg Television, and Wall Street Week with Louis Rukeyser. Articles by and about Wriston were published in many periodicals, including American Banker, American Politics, Barron's, Business Week, the Cato Journal, Chief Executive, Christian Science Monitor, City Journal, Computers in Banking, the Economist, Emerging Market Strategy, the Far Eastern Economic Review, Finance, the Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, Forbes, Foreign Affairs, Fortune, the Harvard Business Review, Intelligencer, New York Newsday Forum, the New York Observer, the New York Times, Reuters World, Time, the Wall Street Journal, and the Washington Post.
  Folders are labeled with the name of the article, the author(s), the title of the publication or program, and the date range of the folder or, if the article is the only item in the folder, the date of the article. Some of the speeches are printed out files extracted from Wriston's computer. Titles in brackets indicate a final publication title followed by Wriston's original computer file name. Wriston's original computer file names were preserved including their dates. When a file date did not correspond to the actual date of the article or interview, the actual date was added.
  The articles and interviews in this series are divided into articles mentioning Walter Wriston, interviews with Mr. Wriston, and articles by Walter Wriston. They are arranged chronologically. Materials accessioned and processed in 2009 are arranged in a second chronological run at the end of the series.
  - Personality: Young Banker in Foreign Service Wriston Is at Helm of National City's Units Abroad by Edward Cowan, The New York Times, 1963-11-24; MS134.003.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - Why Citibank is More Than a Bank by [Unknown Author], Business Week, 1968-11-16; MS134.003.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - Banker of the Year by [Unknown Author], Finance, 1970-10; MS134.003.025.00003; Gunn, John Oliver (Box 25)
    This article was originally published in Finance Magazine in October, 1970.
  - Wriston: The Leadership Comes From Citicorp by [Unknown Author], Business Week, 1973-09-15; MS134.003.025.00004 (Box 25)
  - The Computer That Calls Itself A Bank: Automation is the key to Citicorp's Push Toward Interstate Banking by Sherry Siegel, Computers in Banking, 1984-03; MS134.003.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - Wriston Set Off an Avalanche in a Glacier-Like Industry by Charles N. Stabler, The Wall Street Journal, 1984-08-30; MS134.003.025.00006 (Box 25)
  - Walter B. Wriston '41 by Nancy Smith, Wesleyan: The Wesleyan University Alumnus, Fall, 1985; MS134.003.025.00007 (Box 25)
  - Roll the Dice and Cross Your Fingers by Benjamin M. Rowland, The New York Times, 1986-12-14; MS134.003.025.00008 (Box 25)
  - Whom do You Call a Friend? by [Unknown Author], New York Newsday, 1986-12-23 -- 1986-12-26; MS134.003.025.00009 (Box 25)
  - This Wired World by George F. Will, The Washington Post, 1989-01-05; MS134.003.025.00010 (Box 25)
  - What Some Prominent New Yorker's Read and HRA's Plan for ID Cards: Is It 'Terrific' or 'Big Brother'? by Emily F. Mandelstam, The New York Observer, 1989-01-25 -- 1989-03-06; MS134.003.025.00011 (Box 25)
    What Some Prominent New Yorker's Read was published on March 6, 1989. HRA's Plan for ID Cards: Is It 'Terrific' or 'Big Brother'? was published on January 30, 1989.
  - Flight of Capital Lies at Root of Latin America Debt Crisis and No 'instant solution' to debt problem by Ron Scherer, The Christian Science Monitor, 1987-03-19 -- 1989-04-07; MS134.003.025.00012 (Box 25)
    No 'instant solution' to debt problem was published on March 19, 1987 and Flight of Capital Lies at Root of Latin America Debt Crisis was published on April 7, 1989.
  - Revitalize the Federal Reserve System: A Dollar can do more for a still solvent bank than it can for a failed one by Felix G. Rohatyn and Lloyd N. Cutler, The Washington Post, 1990-12-16 -- 1991-01-08; MS134.003.025.00013 (Box 25)
    The article was published December 16, 1991.
  - Catch-22: The Retired CEO as Company Director by Howard D. Sherman, Institutional Shareholder Services, Inc., 1991-07-15; MS134.003.025.00014 (Box 25)
  - For Chief Executives, Two Ways to Cross Retirement's Bridge by Barbara Lyne, The New York Times, 1993-04-25; MS134.003.025.00015 (Box 25)
  - Wriston's Bum Rap by Martin S. Fridson, Extra Credit & Emerging Strategy, 1995-07 -- 1995-09-28; MS134.003.025.00016 (Box 25)
    The article was published August 24, 1995.
  - Don't Bank on the Fed to Ease Future Schools by George Melloan, The Wall Street Journal, 1995-11-27; MS134.003.025.00017 (Box 25)
  - Default? Never! Alexander Hamilton could have taught a thing or two to Newt, Bill & Co. by Robert Sobel, Barron's, 1996-01-01 -- 1996-02-01; MS134.003.025.00018 (Box 25)
    The article was published January 1, 1996.
  - Walter Wriston: Building a Global Financial Services Business Through Communications and Meritocracy by Steven I. Davis, Leadership in Financial Services: Lessons for the Future, 1996-03-15; MS134.003.025.00019 (Box 25)
    The photocopy of the book excerpt was added to this folder on August 28, 2007.
  - Intelligencer by Beth Landman Keil and Deborah Mitchell, New York Magazine, 1996-05-30 -- 1996-06-03; MS134.003.025.00020 (Box 25)
    The article was published June 3, 1996.
  - Don't Say Retired: Walter Wriston Is Wired by Andrew Serwer, Fortune, 1999-04-12; MS134.003.025.00021 (Box 25)
  - Theme and Profile Investing by Bob Farrell, Merrill Lynch, 1999-12; MS134.003.025.00022 (Box 25)
  - Brooding Over Shifts On Main Street and Wall Street: Six Who Helped Shape Corporate Landscape Find Faults by Robert D. Hershey, Jr., The New York Times, 2000-12-18; MS134.003.025.00023 (Box 25)
  - Reflections on a Master by Peter Huber, Forbes, 2004-04-26; MS134.003.025.00024 (Box 25)
  - Leader Remembers Appleton Roots by Pete Bach, The Post-Crescent Newspaper (Appleton, Wisconsin), 2004-07-12 -- 2004-07-15; MS134.003.025.00025 (Box 25)
    The article was published July 15, 2004.
  - Interview, Meet the Press, 1975-04-20; MS134.003.025.00026 (Box 25)
    This is a television interview.
  - Interview, Face the Nation, 1980-03-23; MS134.003.025.00027 (Box 25)
  - Hi-Tech Capitalism, Opinions, UK Channel 4 Television, 1986-07-24; MS134.003.025.00028 (Box 25)
    This is a television interview. The only item in this folder is a transcript of Walter Wriston's speech. There is a DVD of the interview in Series 4, box 31, item #00003, and barcode: 39090014010363.
  - Comments by Walter B. Wriston, Marketplace - American Public Media [On Mr. Wriston's book "The Twilight of Sovereignty"], 1992-09-16; MS134.003.025.00029 (Box 25)
    This is a radio interview.
  - Interview, Forbes Fact and Comment, 1993-08-24; MS134.003.025.00030 (Box 25)
    This is a phone interview.
  - The Impact of Enron, Lou Dobbs Moneyline CNN, 2002; MS134.003.025.00031 (Box 25)
  - Interview, Meet the Press, 2002-08-08 -- 2002-08-29; MS134.003.025.00032 (Box 25)
    This television interview was broadcasted on August 11, 2002. There is a DVD of the interview in Series 4, box 31, item #00014, and barcode: 39090014010363.
  - Interview, Louis Rukeyser's Wall Street, 2002-08-08 -- 2002-09-10; MS134.003.025.00033 (Box 25)
    This television interview was broadcasted on September 13, 2002.
  - Interview, Bloomberg Television, 2004-03-29 -- 2004-04-02; MS134.003.025.00034 (Box 25)
    This television interview was broadcasted on April 2, 2004. There is a DVD of the interview in Series 4, box 31, item #00024, and barcode: 39090014010363.
  - Interview, Lou Dobbs Tonight, 2004-03-26 -- 2004-04-08; MS134.003.025.00035 (Box 25)
    This is a television interview. There is a DVD of the interview in Series 4, box 31, item #00023, and barcode: 39090014010363.
  - History with Citibank/Industry/Credit Cards & What it is Today-Have You Written a Book on Credit Cards?, New York Times TV, 2004-04-20 -- 2004-04-27; MS134.003.025.00036 (Box 25)
    This is a television interview. In addition, a portion of the interview was published on the PBS Frontline website called the Secret History of the Credit Card.
  - A Conversation with Walter Wriston and Governor Hugh Carey, The Idea Channel, 2004-04-30 -- 2004-05-03; MS134.003.025.00037 (Box 25)
    This is a television interview. There is a DVD of the interview in Series 4, box 31, item #00019, and barcode: 39090014010363.
  - Interviews, The Idea Channel, 2004-02-25 -- 2005-02-15; MS134.003.025.00038 (Box 25)
    There are six interviews with Walter Wriston and The Idea Channel. There are DVDs of the interviews in Series 4, box 31, item #00016 - 00022, and barcode: 39090014010363.
  - Free Trade v. the New Protectionism, by [Unknown Author], Time, 1971-05-10; MS134.003.025.00039 (Box 25)
    This is a published interview.
  - The New Dollar: Meaning of the Devaluation at Home and Abroad Interview with Walter Wriston by [Unknown Author], U.S. News & World Report, 1973-03-26; MS134.003.025.00040 (Box 25)
  - Champion of the Citi: Walter Wriston by Peter Field and Nigel Adam, Euromoney, 1983-10; MS134.003.025.00041 (Box 25)
    This is a published interview. The interview was incomplete. It consisted of only pages 298, 299, and 305. A complete copy of the interview was acquired through interlibrary loan and included in the file.
  - Walter Wriston: An Individual Retirement Account by Steven Solomon, Manhattan Inc., 1985-05; MS134.003.025.00042 (Box 25)
  - Walter Wriston: Deregulation in U.S. Overwhelmingly Positive, Too Slow in Japan by Richard Katz, Diamond Weekly, 1985-12-12 -- 1986-02-21; MS134.003.025.00043 (Box 25)
    This interview was published January 18, 1986.
  - Interest-Free Advice for Uncle Sam with Walter B. Wriston, by [Unknown Author], Newsday, 1986-09-24; MS134.003.025.00044 (Box 25)
  - Is there Virtue in Profit?, Forum with Lewis H. Lapham, Michael Novak, Walter B. Wriston, Robert Lekachman, Peter Steinfels, Harper's Magazine, 1986-12; MS134.003.025.00045 (Box 25)
  - Time Magazine Interview [Not Published], 1989-10-10; MS134.003.025.00046 (Box 25)
    This is an interview.
  - Whatever Happened to Walter Wriston by William B. King, Bank Director: The Publication for Directors of Financial Institutions, 1993; MS134.003.026.00001 (Box 26)
  - Interview with Walter Wriston with John Metzger, Oral History for the LaGuardia and Wagner Archives, 1994-02-23 -- 1994-04-15; MS134.003.026.00002 (Box 26)
    This interview was made for the Abraham D. Beame Collection at LaGuardia and Wagner Archives.
  - Wriston of Citigroup is Still Plugged In by [Unknown Author], FutureBanking, 1996; MS134.003.026.00003 (Box 26)
  - Global Governance: Are Global Institutions A Match for Global Markets, Comments by Walter B. Wriston, Reuters Forum: Human Capital-At the Crossroads of Globalization and the Information Age, 1997-12-08 -- 1998-02-11; MS134.003.026.00004 (Box 26)
    This is a Reuters forum. The forum was held on February 11, 1998.
  - Reflections on Leadership: An Interview with Walter B. Wriston, Citigroup CEO (Retired) by William D. Reisel, Business: The Economy and World Affairs A Reader, 2002-11 -- 2004; MS134.003.026.00005 (Box 26)
    This is interview was published in 2003/2004.
  - Business Statesman Speaks Out on Corporate Crime and the Regulatory Response: Interview with Walter Wriston by [Unknown Author], Directorship, 2004-01; MS134.003.026.00006 (Box 26)
    Interviews; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Real Power by A. J. Vogel, Across the Board, 2005-01 -- 2005-02; MS134.003.026.00007; Vogl, A.J. (Box 26)
  - Tanker Financing For Independent Operators by Walter B. Wriston, The Oil Forum, 1955-11; MS134.003.026.00008 (Box 26)
  - The Drive for Exports by Walter B. Wriston, American Banker, 1963-08-01; MS134.003.026.00009 (Box 26)
  - Report to the President of the United States from the Task Force on Promoting Increased Foreign Investment in United States Corporate Securities And Increased Foreign Financing for United States Corporations Operating Abroad, 1964-04-27; MS134.003.026.00010 (Box 26)
    Walter Wriston was a member of the Task Force on Promoting Increased Foreign Investment in United States Corporate Securities And Increased Foreign Financing for United States Corporations Operating Abroad.
  - First Glance at BOP Program is Fine, But Administration's Borrowing Time by Walter B. Wriston, American Banker, 1966-02-28; MS134.003.026.00011 (Box 26)
  - New York Times Article [Not Published], 1970-04-15; MS134.003.026.00012 (Box 26)
  - Freedom Controls by Walter B. Wriston, New York State Bar Journal, 1973-04; MS134.003.026.00013 (Box 26)
  - My Turn: An Economic Police State by Walter B. Wriston, Newsweek, 1975-05-05 -- 1975-11-17; MS134.003.026.00014; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 26)
    The article was published in Newsweek on May 5, 1975.
    Regulation and markets; Free enterprise